http://www.guitar-dreams.com/privacy

Guitar Dreams Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and I want you to know that this isn't one of those annoying sites that will sell your information or otherwise do annoying things with your information.
It is Guitar Dreams's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.
The registration on this site is simple by design, so that you don't need to provide anything other than an email address and password. When registering through a social site like Facebook, the only information that is being taken from your social account is your name and email address.
Your email address will be used from time to time, for example to send you notifications about new content if you consented during registration. You will be able to unsubscribe from any notifications.
We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
We are committed to conducting business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Guitar Dreams may change this privacy policy from time to time, but what will always remain true is that we won't use your infomation in any sort of annoying way - this just isn't one of those sites!
